{
    "id": "f3799fbc1e624a6697ba57b38d8f3ac5",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The doctor suggested ........................................ take a vacation.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the patient to",
                "that the patient should",
                "that the patient to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Learning ........................................... isn’t easy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "French",
                "the French"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I need .............................................. sleep.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "a good"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We had ............................................. time on the top of the mountain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "great",
                "a great"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am going to the hospital to see a friend who has undergone .......................................... operation.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the",
                "an",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The more you read the ........................................... you understand.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "On the way home, I saw an old beggar accompanied ............................................ a child.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Will you please .................................................. me a copy of ‘The Old Man and the Sea’?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lend",
                "borrow"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The man who knocked ............................................. the door was a stranger.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the difference .............................................. these cars?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "between",
                "among"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}